Guide to the Lahiton - Cinema World image archive M2036
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4: Foreign visitors to Israel/Foreign celebrities
  - Reynolds, Debbie (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Rice Davies, Mandy (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Richard, Cliff (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Robards, Jason (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Rodrigues, Amalia (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Roshdi, Faiza (Egyptian-Jewish singer) (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Ross, Katherine (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Rountree, Richard (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Roussos, Demis (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Sailor (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Saint, Eva Marie (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Sanda, Dominique (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Santana, Carlos (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Savalas, Telly (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Schneider, Romy (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Schwarzenegger, Arnold (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Schygulla, Hanna (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Scorpion (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Segal, George (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Seymour, Jane (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Sharif, Omar (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Shaw, Robert (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Sheen, Martin (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Sheridan, Tony (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Shields, Brooke (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Shocking Blue (Dutch band) (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Shore, Dinah (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Simon & Garfunkel (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Sinatra, Barbara (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Siouxsie and the Banshees (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Paul L. (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Soray, Turkan (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Soul, David (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Steiger, Rod (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Stewart, Rod (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Stone, Sly (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Strauss, Peter (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
  - Streisand, Barbra (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Sutherland, Donald (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Taylor, Elizabeth and Richard Burton (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Torres, Jaime (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Townsend, Jill (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Ullman, Liv (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Vaccaro, Brenda (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Vadim, Roger (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Ventura, Lino (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Voight, Jon (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Voyagis, Yorgo (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Walken, Christopher (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Wallach, Eli (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Welles, Orson (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Williams, Anson (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Wilson, Jennifer (British TV) (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Winger, Debra (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Woods, James (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - York, Michael (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Series 5: Journalists/Politicians/Military
  Images of Israeli and foreign journalists; images of political and military leaders
  - Arbel, Yoram (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Avnery, Uri (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Ben-Ishai, Ron (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Hilary (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Etgar, Avi (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Halabi, Rafik (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Kanar, Dan (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Kanar, Dan (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Lapid, Yosef (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Livni, Yitshak (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Mazor, Dalia (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Peer, Daniel (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Raz, Sari (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Shilon, Dan (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Simon, Bob (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Yavin, Chaim (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Barak, Ehud (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Begin, Menachem (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Dayan, Moshe (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Flatto-Sharon, Shmuel (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Lahat, Shlomo (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Meir, Golda (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
  - Navon, Yitzhak (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Nof, Akiva (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Peres, Shimon (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Rabin, Yitzhak (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Rehavam, Zeevi (Gandhi) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Shamir, Yitzhak (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Sharon, Ariel (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Weizman, Ezer (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Series 6: Military entertainment
  - Sub-series 1: Solo performers
    Images of solo artists performing for military audiences
    - Aloni, Miri (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Arazi, Yardena (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Bahat, Avi (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Bashan, Yigal (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Beger, Mani (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Bodo, Yaacov (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Brandt, Mike (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Burstyn, Mike (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Chen, Shula (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Cohen, Albert (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Gaon, Yehoram (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Havkin, Drora (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Kol, Itsik (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Luka, Jeta (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Lupo (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Marks, Aviva (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Meroz, Guy (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Milo, Yosef (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Moshe, Chaim (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Navon, Ruti (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Reuveni, Dorit (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Soul, David (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Toledano, Avi (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Topaz, Dudu (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Sub-series 2: Bands
    Images of the military bands of various branches and divisions
    - Lahakat ha-nahal (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Ha-tothanim (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Hel ha-avir (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Hel ha-yam (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 5-7)
    - Lahakat havai handasah keravit (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Ha-shiryon (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Ha-tothanim (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Hel ha-avir (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Hel ha-yam (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 5-7)
    - Pikud darom (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - "Pikud Dizengof" (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Pikud hadrakhah (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Pikud ha-merkaz (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Pikud tsafon (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Police bands (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Tsevet havai golani (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Tsevet havai sinai (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Tsevet havai tsanhanim (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Tshizbatron (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Series 7: Miscellaneous categories
  Images grouped into categories by the collector; categories singled out for their interest or importance
  - Advertising (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Airports (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Ambassadors (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Amusement parks (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Animals (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Architects (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Art (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Buildings (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Businesspeople (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Child singers (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Coffee houses (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Dance (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Dance: Yonatan Karmon (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Doctors (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Eyeglasses (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Fans (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Fashion models (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Impresarios: Talit, Yehuda (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Impresarios: Turgeman, Marko (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Impresarios: Weintraub, Simon (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Impresarios: Misc. (Box 45, Folder 8-10)
  - Martial arts (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Nathan, Abie (Voice of Peace) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - People wearing pendants (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Photographers (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Radio (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Records (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Smokers (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Sport: Kattash, Oded (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Swimsuits (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Wedding photos/Lifecycle events (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Series 8: Music
  - Sub-series 1: Bands
    Images of Israeli bands, both candid and promotional
    - Beat bands (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Benzin (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Benzin/Tislam in concert (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Bootleg Beatles (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - The Churchills (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Gazoz (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Gevatron (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Ha-ahim veha-ahayot (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Ha-berirah ha-tivit (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Ha-halonot ha-gevohim (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Ha-kol over habibi (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Hamsin (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Ha-noar ha-oved (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Ha-neshamot ha-tehorot (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Ha-od (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Ha-shagririm (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Ha-shelosharim (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Hedva (Amrani) & David (Tal) (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Jerusalem beat bands (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Kaveret (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
    - Kelim sheluvim (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Kolbo shalom (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Lehakat tsofe Tel Aviv (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Libi and the Flash (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Lo Ikhpat lahem (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Mashinah (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Sexta (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Shokolad mentah mastik (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Shuki & Avivah (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Shuki & Dorit (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Tango ve-alon (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Tislam (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Tsemed ha-raim (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Tzvika Pik bands (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Yalde ha-shemesh (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Yam Yam (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Yemim tovim (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Sub-series 2: Industry photos
    A small number of images relating to Bet ACUM (the Israeli union of music composers and publishers); recording sessions; and recording studios
    - Bet ACUM (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Recording sessions (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Recording studios (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Sub-series 3: Performers
    Images of Israeli solo performers
    - Adam (Chaim Cohen) (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Adam, Zmira (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Adar, Shimon (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Aharon, Shulamit (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Aharony, Ron (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Akerling, Ofer (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Alal, Corinne (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Alberstein, Chava (Box 50, Folder 8-11)
    - Alexandra (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Aloni, Miri (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
    - Amdursky, Benny (Box 51, Folder 4-5)
    - Ami (?) (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Amrani, Hedva (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Anavi, Irit (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Ankory, Margalit (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Arad, Haya (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Arazi, Yardena (Box 52, Folder 2-5)
    - Arbel, Nava (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Argov, Zohar (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Ariel, Meir (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Arnon, Mordechai (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Aroni, Hanna (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Artzi, Shlomo (Box 53, Folder 1-7)
    - Atari, Gali (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Avital, Ilana (Box 54, Folder 2-6)
    - Aviv, Aliza (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Aviv, Mutsi (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Azikri, Aliza (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Bachar, Roni (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Badishi, Sarah (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Bahat, Avi (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Bahunker, Ronen (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Bakar, Moshe (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Baldi, Olier (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Barak, Yosi (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Bashan, Yigal (Box 55, Folder 8-12)
    - Bechar, Ronali (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Becher, Itsik (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Beger, Mani (Box 56, Folder 3-4)
    - Ben, Zehava (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Ben-Shahar, Ilan (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Ben Zeev, Dori (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Berman, Benny (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Bikel, Ruti (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Bolka, Irit (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Boni, Yair (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Bornstein, Niv (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Borodo, Tzvi (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Bosmi, Nava (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Brandt, Mike (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Broza, David (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Bruchin, Nava (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Bums, Zvi (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Carlebach, Shlomo (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Caspi, Matti (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Chaim, Racheli (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Chaim, Racheli (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Chen, Ruby (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Chen, Shula (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Chen, Zmira (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Cohen, Mazi (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, Meir (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Cohen, Yizhar (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Damari, Shoshana (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Dana International (Sharon Cohen) (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Danoch, Rami (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Datz, Orna (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Dotan, Irit (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Eckstein, Gary (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Efroni, Yehuda (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Ekerling, Ofer (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Einstein, Arik (Box 58, Folder 3-7)
    - Elboim, Yehuda (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Eldad, Roni (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Elharar, Dudu (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Elias, Yehuda (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Eliazarov, Dalia (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Eliran, Ron (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Elkanovich, Natan (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Elkayam, Jacky (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Epstein, Yaron (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Eshed, Noga (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Ettinger, Amos (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Fleischer, Moti (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Fortis, Rami (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Fuks, Alonah (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Fuks, Uzi (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Gabai, Aliza (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Gadassi, Avner (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Gal, Nira (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Galil, Esther (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Ganem, Avner (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Gavrielov, Miki (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Geffen, Aviv (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Geffen, Yehonatan (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Golan, Dani (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Golan, Eyal (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Gov, Gidi (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Granot, Danny (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Grinspan, Yehudit (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Gronich, Shlomo (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Gvirtz, Reuven (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Haim, Idit (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Hanoch, Shalom (Box 60, Folder 8-10)
    - Hason, Moshik (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Havkin, Drora (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Haza, Ofra (Box 61, Folder 1-4)
    - Heyman, Si (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Hillel, Moshe (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Hitman, Uzi (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Ilanit (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Kanar, Avner (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Kaniel, Noam (Box 61, Folder 10-12)
    - Kaplan, Aharon (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Kaplan, Yermi (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Kariv, Uri (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Karpel, Avi (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Kenan, Rafi (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Keshet, Sar-Shalom (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Kleinstein, Rami (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Klepter, Vered (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Klepter, Yitzhak (Box 62, Folder 9-11)
    - Klinger, Yair (Box 62, Folder 12-13)
    - Koren, Mili (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Kraus, Shmulik (Box 63, Folder 1-3)
    - Krispin, Geri (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Krivoshei, David (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Krivoshei, Israela (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Kutner, Yoav (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Lavie, Arik (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Lev, Edna (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Levi, Oshik (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Liora (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Livnai, Hani (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Luzon, Eli (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Magen, Eli (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Mahpud, Michael (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Maika, Jacky (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Manor, Ehud (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Manor, Riki (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Maroz, Guy (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Masuri, Eitan (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Matos, Avi (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Mazar, Doron (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Mazar, Doron (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Mekaiten, Jacky (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Menashe, David (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Mercedes (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Miller, Suzi (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Miller, Yonatan (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Miran, Mili (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Mizmor, Tomer (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Mizrahi singers (Box 64, Folder 10-11)
    - Moil, Dudu (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Mor, Gidi (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Mor, Shimon (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Moshe, Chaim (Box 65, Folder 4-6)
    - Muli, Shai (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Musa, Zuzu (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Nadler, Benny (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Nameri, Yoni (Box 65, Folder 10-11)
    - Natan, Shuli (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Navon, Ruti (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
    - Netanela (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Netzer, Effi (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Neuman, Shmuel (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Nir, Aviva (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Nir, Rami (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Nissim, Offer (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Nitzan, Shlomo (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Noi, Michal (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Nottea, Motti (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Ofarim, Avi (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Oleartshik, Alon (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Oshrat, Kobi (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Ozeri, Ahuva (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Pik, Tzvika (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Poliker, Yehuda (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Rabinovich, Nira (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Raveh, Ilka (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Raz, Rika (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Raz, Ruhama (Box 67, Folder 7-8)
    - Recht, Kobi (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Rechter, Yoni (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Rekem, Anat (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Reuven, Erez (Box 67, Folder 12-13)
    - Reuvani, Dorit (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Reznik, Miril (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Ribisi, Gabi (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Rita [Yahan-Farouz] (Box 68, Folder 4-5)
    - Robas, Danny (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Robina, Ilana (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Roni (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Rosenberg, Shuli & Naomi (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Rosenfeld, Tamar (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Rotem, Shosh (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Roter, Haim (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Rudich, Arik (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Sadeh, Michael (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Sadeh, Yoshi (Tislam) (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Sanderson, Danny (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Segev, Jacki (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Segev, Moshe (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Seroussi, Nisim (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Shabat, Shlomi (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Shalom, Israel (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Shamir, Astar (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Shamir, Ephraim (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Shapira, Limor (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Sharabi, Boaz (Box 70, Folder 1-3)
    - Sharabi, Yael (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Sharon, Gidi (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Sharon, Roman (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Sharon, Sarah (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Sharr, Yoel (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Shaul, Yoav (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Shavit, Ami (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Shemer, Naomi (Box 71, Folder 1-3)
    - Shemer, Yoav (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Shemesh, Racheli (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Sheri (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Shevach, Uri (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Shoham, Yonit (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Shor, Meira (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Shoshan, Gabi (Box 71, Folder 10-13)
    - Shoshi, David (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Shoval, Gitit (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Shushan, Danny (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Shvarts, Yehudit (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Sinai, Arik (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Sinvani, Michael (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Spielman, Udi (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Stalos (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Strauss, Avner (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Tal, Michal (Box 72, Folder 10-11)
    - Tamir, Yehuda (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Tavor, Vik (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Tavori, Shimi (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Termin, Nitza (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Tesler, Monika (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Toledano, Avi (Box 73, Folder 1-3)
    - Tovi, Yaakov (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Tsiyon, Golan (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Tubi, Nitza (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Tzanani, Margalit (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Tzuriel, Sarai (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Yagil, Gadi (Box 73, Folder 9-12)
    - Yaniv, Orly (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Yarkoni, Yaffa (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Zarai, Rika (Box 74, Folder 3-4)
    - Zarenkin, Tzipi (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Zer, Benny (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Zer, Dudu (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Zer, Rani (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Zilber, Ariel (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Zohar, Rivka (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Series 9: Television
  - Sub-series 1: Channels & programs
    Images pertaining to Israeli television channels and programs
    - 1, 2, 3, Bul 1, 2, 3, בול (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Admat merivah אדמת מריבה (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Ahare ha-tsiltsul אחרי הצילצול (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Anashim be-mil אנשים במיל (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Aruts Brizah ארוץ בריזה (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Aruts ha-yeladim ארוץ הילדים (Box 75, Folder 6-7)
    - Ba-bayit shel fistuk בבית של פיסטוק (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Bayit patuah בית פתוח (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Beli sodot בלי סודות (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Bubatron בובטרון (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Dizengof 99 דיזנגוף (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Eli ve-Mariano אלי ומריאנו (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Erets moledet ארץ מולדת (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Erets tropit yafah ארץ טרופית יפה (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Ezeh keta איזה קטע (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Florentin פלורנטין (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Ha-mahsan shel ke-ilu המחסן של כאילו (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Ha-mivtsar המבצר (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Ishah hayelet אישה חיילת (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Kadur poreah כדור פורח (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Kafeh pariz קפה פריז (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Kerovim kerovim קרובים קרובים (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Mah she-ba מה שבא (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Medinat ha-yeladim מדינת הילדים (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 14-16)
    - Odelia (Pirate TV station, 1981) אודליה (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Ot ha-paam אות הפעם (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Ot ve-od אות ועוד (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Parpar nehmad פרפר נכמד (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Public service (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Ramat Aviv gimel רמת אביב ג (Box 77, Folder 6-7)
    - Shirat ha-sirenah שירת הסירנה (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Shirutrom (sponsored by Lahiton, 3/30/85) שירותרום (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Skandal ha-mishpahah סקנדל המשפחה (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Yesh gevul יש גבול (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Zeh hu zeh זה הוא זה (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Sub-series 2: Actors
    Images of television actors
    - Banai, Orna (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Bar, Sendi (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Barak, Shimon (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Hadar, Tzvika (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Lavie, Efrat (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - London, Yaron (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Nagar, Lilit (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Nisim, Viktor (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Omer, Nuli (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Pines, Guy (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Reiten, Efrat (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Sassover, Gil (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Segev, Itai (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Shiloah, Yosef (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Yannai, Michael (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Series 10: Theater
  - Sub-series 1: Actors
    Images of theater actors
    - Amir, Yermi (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Amrani, Gabi (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Atsmon, Shemuel (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Azikri, Nissim (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Cohen, Albert (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Cohen, Shimon (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Cohen, Yaffa (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Dattner, Nathan (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Gorlizki, Ili (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Harifai, Zahrira (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Hezkiah, Yitshak (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Hezkiyahu, Avner (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Horgal, Moshe (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Israeli, Razia (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Kafri, Ezra (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Kam, Miki (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Kenig, Leah (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Khoury, Makram (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Lantset, Batia (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Lavi, Shai (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Leiba, Yoel (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Levin, David (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Limon, Dina (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Litai, Dani (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Lubitz, Fania (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Luka, Gita (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Meir, Margalit (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Meiri, Irit (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Marks, Aviva (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Markus, Rachel (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Meron, Hanna (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
    - Milo, Yosef (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Mimes (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Mor, Avraham (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Mor, Tikvah (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Neeman, Bracha (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Neeman, Hillel (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Nitai, Niko (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Noy, Yakov (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Nuni, Geula (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Rabinovich, Nira (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Raz, Rivka (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Robina, Ilana (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Rot, Hannah (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Taylor, Rafi (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Theater actors C-H (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Theater actors K-L (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Theater actors M (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Theater actors: N-S (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Theater actors: T-Z (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Theater managers (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Varshavski, Menashe (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Vishinsky, Shlomo (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Volk, Rachel (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Weingarten, Itsik (Box 82, Folder 7)